Arnold Jin

FULL-STACK / E-Commerce DEVELOPER

Gmail: freelance1773@gmail.com, Telegram: @tinyHelper712, Skype: live:.cid.9e2f3680ddbc5cb5

Skilled and motivated full-stack developer with 6+ years of experience.

Created 40+ websites using several programming languages and frameworks. Advanced in many languages and frameworks such as JavaScript/React/Next/Vue and Python/Django/Flask.

Have a deep knowledge of many high-level programming languages and related fra meworks (I mostly use MERN and Python/Django stack, but seek overall skill vs specific expertise).

Built 10+ E-Commerce websites using Shopify, Magento, and Headless CMS (Strapi, Contentful).

Own the development of product features end-to-end including scoping, architecting, coding, testing, and rolling out features.

EXPERIENCE

Apr 2022 - Present

Full-stack Developer, Self-Employed

- Improved eCommerce web app performance by +18% using ImageEngine for React
- Reduced response time 8.21s to fewer 3s and made real-time chats secure using SSL by NextJS
- Developed highly interactive web applications while integrating Restful APIs and external web services, ensuring high performance.
- Built 4 customized node.js modules integrated with social APIs and deployed projects on AWS

Aug 2019 - Apr 2022

Senior Full-stack Developer, C&F

- Implemented features for the main site and internal applications using React/Redux , NextJS, Node, and Django with RESTAPI.
- Improved and upgraded the development tooling and workflow for several projects (Node.js, Express).

- Integrated platforms with various cloud services and third-party APIs, including Amazon S3, PayPal, AWS Lambda, and Mongo Cluster.
- Built E-Commerce website using NextJS and Strapi and deployed it by DigitalOcean.
- Worked on the payments team to save time and improve cash flow for over 50,000 through the development of modern, responsive customer experiences.
- Established reusable & responsive React chart components using D3.js that support interactive visualizations of data and analysis.
- Used Elastic search engine on AWS to speed up web page performance and React Hooks to prevent unnecessary re-renders.

Jan 2016 - July 2019

Junior Front-end Developer, ANGI

- Created a survey engine supporting different types of questions and views.
- Introduced new media to the company's production team.
- Supported the hosting and management of a client base of 300+ websites.
- Created a web app MVP for a store delivery management platform with 200+ business customers to create, manage, and monitor deliveries using React and Redux.
- Added features to meditation app with 5,000+ monthly users, enabling audio and video uploads using Amazon S3 bucket.

EDUCATION

Warsaw University of Technology, Poland

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science 2012 - 2016

SKILLS

Languages

- JavaScript/TypeScript
- Python
- HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap5

Frameworks & Libraries

- Node.js
- React/Redux
- Vue.js

- Next.js, Nuxt.js
- Django/Flask

Database

- MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQLite
- MongoDB, Oracle, Amazon DynamoDB
- Firebase

AWS & E-Commerce Tools & CMS

- AWS Lamda, AWS S3, AWS EC2
- Shopify, Magento, Strapi
- Salesforce, SFCC, SFSC, Salesforce CRM, API2Cart

Paradigms & Tools

- Scrum, Agile
- CI/CD
- SOLID, DRY, KISS
- Unit Testing, TDD
- Jira/BitBucket, Github, ClickUp
- Postman